Let's start this video and we are going to talk about
ICC Lombard General
Insurance Company Limited. The
company provides many
insurances apart from non-life insurance. If we talk about the
current price of the company, it is
1077. If we look at today's decline,
we have seen a decline of 4.75%. A
huge decline of Rs 53.75 paise has been
seen in the city today. Before this, if we
look at yesterday's rise,
we will know in the five-day chart. If you
look at this place here,
we can see the rise here. Now the
reason behind this rise was that the
numbers were expected, that is,
from the numbers of Q3, sorry Q4, the numbers of the March 2023
quarter, it was estimated
that the company's numbers would be
good,
but there was a slight decrease in the
amount of premium that the company should have received, the
premium in the amount, that is, the
premium of the insurance is the money.  The
company has not
received the amount, apart from that, everything has been
in the company's fever, the profit is also
increasing around 40%, that is, a big
jump has been seen in it, so we are going to discuss the same thing,
apart from that, if we talk about returns, then
in the last 6 months, a return of 6.59% is
seen, in the meantime, the
level of around 1300 was also touched by the stock, if we
talk about 1 year, then in 1 year, a decline of 20% is
seen in the market stock,
this decline from the recent level of Rs 1400 is seen
in the city, if we
talk about five years, then in 5 years, we get to see a
modest return of 38-39% i.e. 40%,
however,
if we look at the higher level, then we get to see this return
going above 100%,
friends,
apart from that, if we talk about maximum return, then it has
given a maximum return of 58%, since the
company's listing is in 2017,  If you look at it, the
returns have not been given further, that is, the
stock has been booked for the long term, that is, for the short
term you can go into this stock,
for the long term you can avoid this stock.
If we look at the lion in the candle stick pattern, there is a
big fall, today
we will see a big red candle forming,
which is around 5%. If we talk about
its
previous day, then a green candle was
seen divided, why it was seen
divided, why it was formed,
I have already told you, the
meaning of eating is that the lion, if we
look at it now, is trading around its support, the
price is Rs. 1076 and
we can see support around ₹105040000,
consider it as support or take it for granted,
which it had placed recently a month or two ago, so the
numbers of the company have
come out good, in such a situation, the brokerage houses, they
also have some count of lions.
We will discuss all that in this video,
as I told you, you
can go into the stock for the short term.
If someone is buying the stock for the long term, then you
can once again pay a little attention to your decision.
Percentage expected premium on ICC Lombard General Insurance,
as I told you,
they have not received the premium in proportion, that is, they have
not received it in the quantity, as per the
expectation here, they should have received it in the quantity,
here we get to see the premium of the brokerage ICC Lombard General Insurance Company, Financial Year 2015 crore in ratio,
now what happens here is that the
company gets a premium of Rs 3726 crore, but the
analysts had
estimated it to be around Rs 4000 crore. So, in such a situation, this
shortfall of around Rs 400 crore is a story,
due to which we can see a decline in the city today.
Apart from that, if we look at the net profit, then
here the net profit is better than the
expected, so the net profit has jumped by 40%,
which is 487 crores, sorry 437 crores, on
view one by basis the company has
generated net profit, the
expectation of 394 crores which was placed
here has beaten the estimate,
however in terms of premium,
due to the decline in Kahaani Na Kahaani Sher, we have seen, if we
talk about total income, then we get to see the total income of
around 5255 crores in this quarter
and we get to see a growth of 13%
in it, have you said about the
company and stop post
your result on global result and broker
positivity on expense
of management
2014, so what I mean to eat is that it is positive,
but at the same time they have taken a course
that the cost of insurance is going to
increase.  Because of that, the
story is that the company of ICC Lombard, which is a
lion, may have to face some problems.
Before that, let us see here the brokerage
Philips ICC Lombard's
limit, its re-rating position about but the
expected profit per
quarter which is activated lower
undertaking loss and higher investment income is
given here and the target price is
kept around 1400.
Now if we talk about the side, then
according to April 18, we have an
upright of 26%, if we
calculate as per today, then we get to see a right of 30% in
it. So the
story together is that whatever
brokerage houses are there, for example, if we
talk about UPSC Security, then they have also
given a rating of brother and also have
given a target of 1455 in it.
Now if we look further from GP Morgan's side, then
their rating here is that they have
given a neutral rating and a target of 1160
along with it.  The
meaning of eating it is that
we are seeing a mixed outcome of the same kind from brokerage houses,
although I personally
believe that the numbers of the company, as
we told, are better than expected, that is, the
company has generated strong numbers, there was a
possibility that the stock would run ahead,
but the market made a premium which the
company did not get in full, that is, the
premium amount which was expected was
not received as per the expectation, due to which
we have seen a fall of up to 5% in the stock today, if we
talk about the price of the stock, it is
around the support, it can be bought for the short term, the
numbers are excellent,
we can see the company performing better.